Haruka Miyagi Web Engineer

✓ h.miyagi4u@gmail.com

♀ Tokushima, Japan

bluesky4u

R Portfolio

PROFILE

Haruka is a software engineer with over 5 years of web development experience.

She has experience both as a team member as well as independently, and has the ability to quickly learn and adapt to new technology environments.

Also, Haruka specialize in the development, testing, and support of various websites, web, and mobile applications.

Currently, she is striving to gain better skills and experience, and is looking for better opportunities in the process.

SKILLS

Programming Languages (PHP, Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, Java, C, Solidity)

Back-end (Laravel, Node, Express, Python)

Front-End (HTML, CSS, React, Vue.js, Ant Design, M-UI, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Web3.js)

Database (MySQL, MongoDB, Firebase Runtime Database, AWS DynamoDB)

DevOps (Git, CI/CD, Docker, AWS, Firebase, Plesk)

Restful APIs (OpenAl API, LangChain, ChatGPT, Stable Diffusion, Text-To-Speech, Speech-To-Text, Text-to-Image, Image-to-Image)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Technological Institute of the Philippines

September 2014 – April 2017 Quezon City, Philippines

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Self-Employeed (Freelancer)

May 2023 – present Japan

Software Engineer

- Mainly developed web systems for business management, customer management, reservation management, and production management using Laravel and MERN.
- Developed EC sites using CMS platforms such as Shopify, WordPress, EC Cube, and Future Shop.
- Solana smart contract development (Unit test, Rust cosmwasm, Solana-program-library, Solana-web3) by using Rust framework
- Developed such tokens as ERC20 token and BEP20 token, ERC721 token, ERC1155 token, etc.

Awesome CX

Web Engineer

- Architected, implemented, and deployed robust web application projects using Laravel(Blade template, L5 repository), WordPress, React + TypeScript, etc. resulting in significant gains in client retention and business growth.
- Designed and built secure and performant RESTful APIs in Node.js, also in python script enabling seamless data flow and communication between frontend and backend.
- NFT minting and NFT marketplace development(Create listing by admin, flat & Crypto payment, etc.)
- Taking part in various ChatGPT development which guarantees high traffic, and enhanced user experience by 23%

Junior Web Developer

- Utilized and implemented 7+ engaging, responsive, and mobile-friendly website contexts and elements.
- Developed and maintained multiple Shopify stores for clients, including customizing themes and creating custom plugins
- Developed AI Chatbot which generates contents of blog and description of products automatically, leading to 16% increase in user and client engagement.
- Front-end development interactive with smart contract by using Web3, truffle, React and Vue.

June 2019 – March 2023 Davao City, Philippines

April 2018 – May 2019 Davao City, Philippines

Circa Logica Group

Web Developer

June 2017 – March 2018 Quezon City, Philippines

- Developed 13+ website layouts using React components, and Laravel (combining Vue.js) for various clients, resulting in a 19% increase in website traffic.
- Developed intuitive, responsive websites utilizing HTML,
 CSS, and JavaScript, complying with industry best practices and accessibility standards.
- Developed single-page applications using React and TypeScript, delivering responsive and user-friendly interfaces for clients.
- Implemented various third-party APIs into web applications, enabling seamless interaction between data sources and services.

UNFORGETTABLE QUOTES

- The secret of success is to do the common thing uncommonly well.
- · First, solve the problem. Then, write the code.
- I never dreamed about success, I worked for it.
- · Nothing is impossible, the word itself says I'm possible!